XINBEI ZHU

(+1) 5409981515 | zhuhelen56@gmail.com | LinkedInURL

Areas of expertise include:		
☐ Programming in Languages ☐ Algorithms Application	□ Event Management □ Data Analysis	☐ Project Management ☐ Public Speaking and Presentations
	Work Expe	RIENCES
Inspur Digital R&D Team; Role: Softwar	e Developer Intern.	Jinan, China, October 2021 - December 2021
Worked as an intern to learn abou Main Contributions:	t natural languages proce	ssing and use Bert model for word similarity analysis.
• Scraped data and keywords parameters of the Bert mod	· · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · ·	e database, and labeled the data. Adjusted the y of the model.
Chinasoft International Technology Service Role: Data Analyst Intern.		Beijing, China, August 2021 - October 2021
Worked as an intern to understand Main Contributions:	d the specific work and af	fairs of a data analyst preliminarily.
2 0	ů,	he data of company's products using classification ag tools like RStudio and Jupyter
	Publicat	TIONS
Dr. Mingqiu Wang, Min Ren, She Asymmetric Least Squares, <i>Spring</i>	9	Robust Optimal Subsampling Based on Weighted 23).

Project Experiences

Assessment for anti-cracking capabilities of the Glaze system

September 2023 - now

Aim to apply state-of-the-art denoising models to the Glaze system to assess its anti-cracking capabilities

Main Work:

- Prepare the dataset for training by ensuring data quality and consistency.
- Review academic papers to identify state-of-the-art denoising models.

Parcel Damage Classification

January 2023 - May 2023

Set out to solve the problem of identifying damaged packages in hopes that such a system will be implemented in a distribution center to automatically identify and mark damaged packages as they pass through.

Main Work:

- Use Google iCrawler to gather custom image dataset and use python script to remove duplicate images.
- Train a YOLO-based model to identify the damaged packages. Incorporate the YOLO pre-trained model into our labelled dataset to develop a novel classification model.
- Build the front-end for classifying damaged and undamaged packages. Develop the front-end interface for package classification utilizing the VGG19 model with a custom top layer, subsequent to a comprehensive evaluation of recall rates and performance across multiple models, including ResNet50, YOLOv5, VisualBERT, and VGG19.

How to Maximize Customer Value Potential?

Client/Sponsor: Grameenphone - Bangladesh

To reduce customers' churn rate, increase customers' lifetime value and maximize revenue.

Main Work:

- Clean the data using Removing Records Method.
- Use Classification Model and K-means Clustering Model to Analyze and Train the Data. Cluster customers into different groups; figure out the likes and dislikes of groups; decide whether to increase or decrease related services based on these criteria.

EDUCATION AND TECHNICAL PROFICIENCY

Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University

Master of Science, Computer Science

Started in Fall 2023

August 2022 - December 2022

Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

2019 - 2023

Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University

Bachelor of Science, Computational Modeling and Data Analytics

2019 - 2023

SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

Technical Skills:

Computer Languages: C, Java, Python, R, Latex Applications & Tools:
Microsoft Office(Word, PowerPoint, Excel)

VS Code, Eclipse, Anaconda, RStdio, Git

Languages:

English
Chinese